=Visage and Soul=
("The Unique Her"
Trilogy on Women's Relationships)
=Episode 15=
Qin Yu.
Do you smell it?
This is the mugwort scent I know best.
Whenever I smell it,
I feel at ease.
It makes me feel like
there's hope for the future.
Then,
is there a place for me
in your future?
Xiaoduo.
I...
Don't get me wrong.
I wasn't...
That's not what I meant.
Let me mark you.
That way, you'll be mine alone.
Really?
Xiaoduo.
What?
Does it really hurt that much?
No, it doesn't hurt.
Go ahead and do it.
I'll let you.
Really, go ahead.
You goof.
By the way, Xiaoduo.
Wait here for me.
I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
It's a surprise.
Wait for me to come back.
Wait for me, Xiaoduo.
Xiaoduo!
No!
Xiaoduo.
Qin Yu.
No!
Wake up, Qin Yu.
Who were you talking to just now?
What did I just say?
Answer my question first.
Who were you talking to just now?
Weren't you talking to Qiao Xiaomi?
You're getting a little too nosy.
I'm telling you.
No matter what I said,
you can't tell anyone.
What secret are you hiding?
I don't have any secrets.
There you are, my MVP.
Come on.
Sit down.
I'm in a great mood today.
Zhiwei.
You got the news pretty fast.
Now you've got
the gallery in your hands too.
Hurry up and get married.
Come.
Let's celebrate in advance.
If we're celebrating,
let's do it properly.
That's the thing your subconscious
cares about most.
Maybe it's also what
you most want to forget.
Why did you come to me? Say something.
If you won't talk, I'm leaving.
I'm really leaving.
Don't do anything stupid.
♪The bud is tinted into wisdom♪
♪Raising butterflies♪
♪Strong and radiant♪
♪Adorning the lilies♪
♪Weaving together clouds and poetry♪
♪Circling at the edge of sunset♪
♪Come walk along my secret path,
my diamond-like heart♪
♪From the ruins rise dazzling thorns♪
♪The footprints of angels and beasts♪
♪They are all a part of me♪
♪Watering these vines
to the ends of the earth♪
♪I am so heavy, yet so rich♪
♪Great disasters, ordinary joys♪
♪Let them drift away with the wind♪
♪In exchange for
the richness of my soil♪
♪Tempering my cold eyes,
scorching my back♪
♪Cast into the ashes,
evolving into islands♪
♪In the end,
I become the one who can weave♪
♪Rivers that wind around♪
♪Watering these vines
to the ends of the earth♪
♪So heavy, yet so rich♪
♪Great disasters, ordinary joys♪
♪Let them drift away with the wind♪
♪In exchange for♪
♪The richness of my soil♪
(What am I doing?)
(Xiaomi.)
(Something came up at the gallery,
so I have to go.)
(Don't forget to eat breakfast.)
(After what happened last night,)
(he just left this morning.)
(He left me here all by myself.)
♪We say good morning, we say good night♪
♪We say we miss each other,
but never speak of the hurt♪
♪The sweeter it is, the luckier we seem♪
♪Yet the more romantic,
the rougher the road♪
♪Let me go, set me free♪
♪Let me drown in reckless silence♪
♪We were perfect for each other,
yet you never admitted it♪
♪The freedom you gave me♪
♪Became the heaviest chain I bear♪
♪Love can barely move forward♪
♪Yet the words still linger unspoken♪
♪The closeness I long for♪
♪There's no need for you
to keep avoiding it♪
♪I don't want to break free♪
♪Take back the chains
disguised as freedom♪